

JUNIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER

PORTFOLIO

PROFILE

Currently, I work as a Technical Leader at Axa XL. On a daily basis I am responsible for process automation. Some time ago, I made a decision to change my career path to IT. I do not have commercial experience, however I am still making new projects on my own. I am a person who is characterized by a 'can-do' attitude and I am always trying to overcome the issue on my own.

I am able to write responsive pages in React or Javascript in line with the newest standards and REST API. Presently, I am focused on making React projects into my personal portfolio and learning Typescript.

HOW TO REACH ME

Phone: +48 662 623 531 Email: marcin.wrzs@gmail.com

City: Wrocław
Github: Marcinwrzs

SKILLS

Programming

React, JavaScript, HTML, CSS (including SASS), API, bootstrap, webpack, github, SQL

Achievements:

Radio Luz: hosting weekly radio show called Ultradzwięki Toastmasters: practicing public speaking skills

Aiesec: marketing promotion of the event Dni Kariery

2017

EDUCATION

Wrocław University of Economics

Master of Finance and Accounting 2017 - 2019

University of Wrocław

Bachelor of National Security 2014 - 2017

PROJECTS

Foodie

Project with recipes written in React with hooks and react-router. components have been styled by styled-components. Project is connected with an external API. Some functions have been moved to the GlobalContext section and handled by Reducers. The slider on the main page has been made by Splidejs. Project has been published at this <u>link</u> by Netify.

Portfolio

Project which depics my resume has been written in React with hooks and react-router. You are able to switch between Day and Night mode, open my resume in the Resume section or send an email by contact form which is supported by the service EmailJS.

<u>Blackjack</u>

Project has been written in HTML, SCSS, Javascript with Object Oriented Programming standards and bundled in the Webpack.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Technical Lead, Broker Accreditation Analyst

Axa XL | January 2023 to present

- building and Improving process areas
- · coordinating process improvement initiatives

Analyst, Senior Financial Services Operations

Factor Law | October 2020 to December 2022

- improving the process by VBA,
- coordinating the work allocation across the Negotiator teams

Security and Pricing Data Management Specialist

Credit Suisse | January 2020 to September 2020

· maintaining data of financial instruments and their prices

Data & Document Specialist

UBS | February 2019 to October 2019

• providing customer service and support to Front Office

Junior Representative, Reconciliation

BNY Mellon | January 2018 to February 2019

- data investigation using information from different vendors
- reconciliation against broker/custodian statements